Guide to the Archives Information File, Section 3: Boxes 46-66
Archives Information File, Section 3: Boxes 46-66
- Box: 65, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Plastics, 1947; Publication (Box 65, Folder 19)
    Notes: January 15, 1947
- Box: 65, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Local 706, Plumbers & Steamfitters Union, 1961; Publication (Box 65, Folder 20)
    Notes: February 6, 1961
- Box: 65, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 65, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Point 4 in Action, Publication (Box 65, Folder 21)
- Box: 65, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 65, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: In Poland Today, Publication (Box 65, Folder 22)
    Author: British Trade Union Delegation to Poland
- Box: 65, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 65, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Poland's Six Year Plan, Publication (Box 65, Folder 23)
    Author: U.S. Embassy: Poland
- Box: 65, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 65, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: The Labour Movement and the Polish Cause, Publication (Box 65, Folder 24)
    Author: Patrick J. Dollan
- Box: 65, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 65, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Social Rights and Facilities in Poland, Publication (Box 65, Folder 25)
    Author: Kazimierz Kakol
- Box: 65, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 65, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Increase Police, Firemen, and Teachers Salaries, 1969; Publication (Box 65, Folder 26)
    Author: Committee on the District of Columbia
    Notes: August 11 & November 19, 1969
  - Item 2: Police Compensation Survey, 1968; Publication (Box 65, Folder 26)
- Box: 65, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 65, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Inhalte und Methoden der Fortbildung won Schutzpolizeibeamten in den Einzeldiensthehorden, Publication (Box 65, Folder 27)
    Author: Verlag fur Polizeiliches Fachschrifttum
- Box: 65, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 65, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Police Unions and Other Police Organizations, 1944; Publication (Box 65, Folder 28)
    Author: International Association of Chiefs of Police
    Notes: September 1944
- Box: 65, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 65, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Retirement Systems for Policemen and Firemen, 1966; Publication (Box 65, Folder 29)
    Author: Montana Legislative Council
- Box: 65, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 65, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: How Your Employee Publication Can Bolster Company Security, 1966; Publication (Box 65, Folder 30)
    Author: Prentice Hall
- Box: 65, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 65, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Salaries and Working Conditions in Rhode Island Police Departments, Publication (Box 65, Folder 31)
- Box: 65, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 65, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: The Police, Publication (Box 65, Folder 32)
  - Item 2: Police Resource Allocation, Publication (Box 65, Folder 32)
    Author: Gordon E. Misner, Richard B. Hoffman
- Box: 65, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 65, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Trade Union Membership, 1962; Publication (Box 65, Folder 33)
    Author: Political and Economic Planning
    Notes: July 2, 1962
- Box: 65, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 65, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: On the Construction of Socialist Evonomy in the Fpry, 1948; Publication (Box 65, Folder 34)
    Author: Boris Kidric
- Box: 65, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 65, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Financing State Senate Campaigns, 1964; Publication (Box 65, Folder 35)
    Author: Donald G. Balmer
- Box: 65, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 65, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Rural Poverty and Hunger, 1968; Publication (Box 65, Folder 36)
    Notes: February 14, 1968
  - Item 2: Poverty Programs and Social Mobility, Publication (Box 65, Folder 36)
    Author: Harold F. Kaufman, Kenneth P. Wilkinson, Lucy W. Cole
  - Item 3: Canadian Welfare Council Staff Submission to the Special Senate Committee on Poverty, 1969; Publication (Box 65, Folder 36)
    Author: Special Senate Committee on Poverty
  - Item 4: Poverty in Canada, Publication (Box 65, Folder 36)
- Box: 65, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 65, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Hungry Children, Publication (Box 65, Folder 37)
- Box: 65, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 65, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: The Facts of Poverty in New York City, 1965; Publication (Box 65, Folder 38)
    Author: Herbert Bienstock
    Notes: March 11, 1965
  - Item 2: The Facts of Poverty, 1965; Publication (Box 65, Folder 38)
  - Item 3: Poverty in New York City, 1964; Publication (Box 65, Folder 38)
    Author: Community Council of Greater New York
- Box: 65, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 65, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: The Incidence of Poverty, 1965; Publication (Box 65, Folder 39)
    Author: Jerry J. Williams, Leo T. Surla
- Box: 65, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 65, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Dimensions of Poverty, 1965; Publication (Box 65, Folder 40)
  - Item 2: A Public Employment Program for the Unemployed Poor, Publication (Box 65, Folder 40)
    Author: Greenleigh Associates
- Box: 65, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 65, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Vocational Rehabilitation and the Socially Disabled, Publication (Box 65, Folder 41)
    Author: Julius S. Cohen, Robert J. Gregory, John W. Pelosi
  - Item 2: Economic Opportunity Act of 1964, 1965; Publication (Box 65, Folder 41)
  - Item 3: Economic Opportunity Amendments of 1965, Publication (Box 65, Folder 41)
    Notes: May 27, 1965
  - Item 4: Teen-Agers Join the War on Poverty, Publication (Box 65, Folder 41)
    Author: Ann G. Wolfe
  - Item 5: Youth and the War on Poverty, Publication (Box 65, Folder 41)
  - Item 6: The Youth We Haven't Served, Publication (Box 65, Folder 41)
  - Item 7: Poverty in the U.S.A., Publication (Box 65, Folder 41)
    Author: J. Stouder Sweet
  - Item 8: The Economic Opportunity Act and Public Welfare, Publication (Box 65, Folder 41)
    Author: Andrew R.N. Truelson
  - Item 9: Impact on Public Assistance Caseloads, 1965; Publication (Box 65, Folder 41)
  - Item 10: A Search for New Directions in the War Against Poverty, Publication (Box 65, Folder 41)
    Author: Harold L. Sheppard
  - Item 11: Effects of Family Planning on Poverty in the United States, Publication (Box 65, Folder 41)
    Author: The W.E. Upjohn Institute
  - Item 12: Urban and Rural Poverty, 1967; Publication (Box 65, Folder 41)
    Notes: March 15, 1967
  - Item 13: Public Employment Program for the Unemployed Poor, Publication (Box 65, Folder 41)
  - Item 14: Anti-Poverty Tools for Urban Renewal, 1965; Publication (Box 65, Folder 41)
    Author: U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development
  - Item 15: The Student and the Forgotten America, Publication (Box 65, Folder 41)
    Author: Rachelle Diener
  - Item 16: A Program for the Low-Income Population at Substandard Levels of Living, 1956; Publication (Box 65, Folder 41)
    Notes: January 5, 1956
  - Item 17: The Incidence and Effects of Poverty in the United States, Publication (Box 65, Folder 41)
    Author: Sociological Resources for the United States
  - Item 18: The American Lower Class Family, Publication (Box 65, Folder 41)
    Author: Suzanne Keller
  - Item 19: Low-Income Life Styles, Publication (Box 65, Folder 41)
  - Item 20: The Poor, Publication (Box 65, Folder 41)
  - Item 21: Office of Economic Opportunity, 1968; Publication (Box 65, Folder 41)
    Author: John B. Regnell
- Box: 65, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 65, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: An Evaluation of Alternative Techniques for Estimating County Population in a Six-State Area, Publication (Box 65, Folder 42)
    Author: Oklahoma State University
- Box: 65, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 65, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Population Facts and Policies, Publication (Box 65, Folder 43)
    Author: Eva M. Hubback
- Box: 65, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 65, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Population and Economic Growth, Publication (Box 65, Folder 44)
- Box: 65, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 65, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Portland Harbor, 1961; Publication (Box 65, Folder 45)
    Author: U.S. Committee on Public Welfare
    Notes: August 7, 1961
- Box: 65, Folder: 46, Publication (Box 65, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: The Decision to Stay, 1966; Publication (Box 65, Folder 46)
    Author: Secratariado Nacional da Informacao
- Box: 65, Folder: 47, Publication (Box 65, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: Opportunity in Portugal, Publication (Box 65, Folder 47)
    Author: General Economic
- Box: 65, Folder: 48, Publication (Box 65, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: Le Travailleur Portugais et la Famille Portugaise en France, Publication (Box 65, Folder 48)
    Author: Service Social D'Aide Aux Emigrants
    Language: French; Portuguese.
- Box: 65, Folder: 49, Publication (Box 65, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: Lernbehelf, 1966; Publication (Box 65, Folder 49)
    Author: Generaldirektion fur die Post- und Telegraphenverwaltung
- Box: 66, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Research, Development, and Mechanization, 1963; Publication (Box 66, Folder 1)
    Author: U.S. Post Office Department
    Notes: February 1963
- Box: 66, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Exempting the Postal Field Service from the Whitten Amendment, 1965; Publication (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Postmaster Appointments, 1969; Publication (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Discipline and Discharge in the United States Postal Service, 1966; Publication (Box 66, Folder 2)
    Author: Harry R. Blaine, Eugene C. Hagburg, Frederick A. Zeller
  - Item 4: RPO Employees, 1967; Publication (Box 66, Folder 2)
    Notes: October 12, 1967
  - Item 5: Irregular, Unscheduled, Overtime Differential for PFS Employees and Two-Step Salary Increase for Employees Moving Between Pay Systems, 1968; Publication (Box 66, Folder 2)
    Notes: February 21 & 27, 1968
  - Item 6: RPO Employees, 1969; Publication (Box 66, Folder 2)
    Notes: May 15, 1969
  - Item 7: Five-Day Week for Postmasters, 1965; Publication (Box 66, Folder 2)
    Notes: July 9, 1965
  - Item 8: Plan of Action, 1968; Publication (Box 66, Folder 2)
- Box: 66, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Postal Reorganization and Salary Adjustment Act, 1970; Publication (Box 66, Folder 3)
    Notes: May 19, 1970
- Box: 66, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Attack on Mass Poverty and Unemployment, Publication (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Who are the Urban Poor?, Publication (Box 66, Folder 4)
    Author: Anthony Downs
  - Item 3: The Facts of Poverty, 1964; Publication (Box 66, Folder 4)
    Notes: April 10, 1964
  - Item 4: An Economic Definition of Poverty, Publication (Box 66, Folder 4)
    Author: Harold W. Watts
  - Item 5: The New Poverty, Publication (Box 66, Folder 4)
    Author: Federal Reserve Bank of Philadelphia
  - Item 6: The War on Poverty, 1964; Publication (Box 66, Folder 4)
    Notes: July 23, 1964
  - Item 7: Labor and the War Against Poverty, Publication (Box 66, Folder 4)
    Author: Hyman Minsky
  - Item 8: Poverty Drive, 1964; Publication (Box 66, Folder 4)
    Author: National Child Labor Committee
  - Item 9: Improvements Needed in the Administration of Contracts for Evaluations and Studies of Antipoverty Programs, 1971; Publication (Box 66, Folder 4)
    Notes: December 28, 1971
- Box: 66, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Selective Perception of Occupational Prestige, 1965; Publication (Box 66, Folder 5)
    Author: Robert W. Hodge, Paul M. Siegel
- Box: 66, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Wholesale Price Indexes, Publication (Box 66, Folder 6)
    Author: Dominion Bureau of Statistics
- Box: 66, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Probable Effects of the Proposed Quality Stabilization Act on Prices, Incomes, Employment, and Production, 1963; Publication (Box 66, Folder 7)
- Box: 66, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: The Office of Price Administration, Publication (Box 66, Folder 8)
    Author: Thomas G. Manning
- Box: 66, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Probable Effects of the Proposed Quality Stabilization Act on Prices, Incomes, Employment, and Production, 1963; Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
- Box: 66, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Government Price Statistics, 1966; Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
- Box: 66, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Prices Received, Parity Index, and Parity Ratio Unchanged, 1964; Publication (Box 66, Folder 11)
    Notes: December 15, 1964
  - Item 2: The Revised Consumer Price Index, 1964; Publication (Box 66, Folder 11)
    Notes: March 6, 1964
  - Item 3: The Statistical Structure of the Revised CPI, Publication (Box 66, Folder 11)
    Author: Sidney A. Jaffe
  - Item 4: Government Price Statistics, 1961; Publication (Box 66, Folder 11)
    Notes: July 21, 1961
  - Item 5: Administered Prices and Inflation, Publication (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Item 6: Prices, Escalation, and Economic Stability, 1971; Publication (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Item 7: The American Lower Class Family, Publication (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Item 8: Wholesale Price Index, 1952; Publication (Box 66, Folder 11)
- Box: 66, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: A Time to Act, Publication (Box 66, Folder 12)
    Author: Joint Commission on Correctional Manpower and Training
- Box: 66, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Problems in Business and Industrial Mobilization, 1951; Publication (Box 66, Folder 13)
    Author: Melvin Anshen
  - Item 2: Production Control in the Small Factory, Publication (Box 66, Folder 13)
- Box: 66, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Production Schedulers, 1944; Publication (Box 66, Folder 14)
    Author: Addison-Wesley Press
- Box: 66, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Some Questions and Answers about Performance Standards, Publication (Box 66, Folder 15)
- Box: 66, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Productivity and Economic Growth, 1960; Publication (Box 66, Folder 16)
    Notes: June 13-16, 1960
  - Item 2: Productivity, Wages, and National Income, Publication (Box 66, Folder 16)
    Author: The Brookings Institution
  - Item 3: Measurement of the Effectiveness of the Productive Unit, Publication (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - Item 4: Trends in Output per Man-Hour in the Private Economy, Publication (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - Item 5: Selected Types of General Industrial Equipment, 1952; Publication (Box 66, Folder 16)
- Box: 66, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: American Productivity: Key to Economic Strength and National Survival, 1972; Publication (Box 66, Folder 17)
    Notes: July 3, 1972
  - Item 2: Data for Measurement of Industrial Productivity in the United States, 1965; Publication (Box 66, Folder 17)
    Author: Leon Greenberg
  - Item 3: Data for Measurement of Industrial Productivity in the United States, 1964; Publication (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - Item 4: Betriebs-Wirtschaftliche Mitteilungen, Publication (Box 66, Folder 17)
    Author: Die Produktivitat
  - Item 5: Comparisons of Indexes of Labor and Nonlabor Payments, Prices, and Output per Man-Hour in the Total Private Economy and the Private Nonfarm Sector, 1965; Publication (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - Item 6: America is Different, 1949; Publication (Box 66, Folder 17)
    Author: Danish Federation of Labor
  - Item 7: Report of the Second Session, 1949; Publication (Box 66, Folder 17)
    Author: Anglo-American Council on Productivity
    Notes: March-April 1949
  - Item 8: Report of the First Session, 1948; Publication (Box 66, Folder 17)
    Notes: November 1948
- Box: 66, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 66, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Employee Cooperation on Productivity, 1951; Publication (Box 66, Folder 18)
    Notes: May 1951
  - Item 2: A Formula for Labor Productivity in Georgia, Publication (Box 66, Folder 18)
    Author: Charles Sewell
  - Item 3: Education and Productivity, Publication (Box 66, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: the Facts of Productivity, 1946; Publication (Box 66, Folder 18)
    Notes: December 6, 1946
- Box: 66, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 66, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Indexes of Output per Man-Hour, 1965; Publication (Box 66, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: Indexes of Output per Man-Hour, Hourly Compensation, and Unit Labor Costs in the Private Sector of the Economy and the Nonfarm Sector, 1967; Publication (Box 66, Folder 19)
  - Item 3: Output Per Man-Hour for Selected Industries, 1962; Publication (Box 66, Folder 19)
  - Item 4: Output Per Man-Hour for Selected Industries, 1960; Publication (Box 66, Folder 19)
  - Item 5: Indexes of Output per Man-Hour, 1964; Publication (Box 66, Folder 19)
    Notes: September 1964
  - Item 6: Mal for Produksjonsenheters Effektivitet, 1969; Publication (Box 66, Folder 19)
    Author: Finn R. Forsund
  - Item 7: Labour-Management Relations and Productivity, Publication (Box 66, Folder 19)
    Author: The Ditchley Foundation
  - Item 8: Improving Productivity and Productivity Measurement in Local Governments, Publication (Box 66, Folder 19)
  - Item 9: Productivity and Technological Trends in the Private Economy, 1963; Publication (Box 66, Folder 19)
  - Item 10: Productivity and Economic Growth, 1960; Publication (Box 66, Folder 19)
  - Item 11: Labor Productivity, 1946; Publication (Box 66, Folder 19)
    Author: L.B. Whieldon
    Notes: September 25, 1946
  - Item 12: Indices of Productivity, Publication (Box 66, Folder 19)
  - Item 13: Management Techniques for Increasing Labor Productivity, 1946; Publication (Box 66, Folder 19)
    Author: American Management Association
  - Item 14: Measurement of Productivity, Publication (Box 66, Folder 19)
  - Item 15: Output per Man-Hour in Selected Manufacturing Industries, 1946; Publication (Box 66, Folder 19)
  - Item 16: Machines and Productivity, Publication (Box 66, Folder 19)
- Box: 66, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 66, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Practical Methods of Increasing Productivity in Manufacturing Industries, 1953; Publication (Box 66, Folder 20)
    Author: International Labour Office
  - Item 2: Productivity and Wage Settlements, Publication (Box 66, Folder 20)
  - Item 3: Indexes of Output per Man-Hour, 1965; Publication (Box 66, Folder 20)
  - Item 4: Productivity, 1960; Publication (Box 66, Folder 20)
  - Item 5: Private and Public Manpower Policies to Stimulate Productivity, Publication (Box 66, Folder 20)
  - Item 6: Conference on Productivity, 1949; Publication (Box 66, Folder 20)
    Notes: June 4, 1949
  - Item 7: "Productivity" from the Worker's Standpoint, 1949; Publication (Box 66, Folder 20)
  - Item 8: Productivity and the Factory Worker, 1947; Publication (Box 66, Folder 20)
  - Item 9: Productivity and the Wage Structure, 1948; Publication (Box 66, Folder 20)
    Author: John T. Dunlop
  - Item 10: Productivity and Unit Labor Cost in Selected Manufacturing Industries, 1946; Publication (Box 66, Folder 20)
  - Item 11: Power, Machines, and Plenty, Publication (Box 66, Folder 20)
    Author: Gloria Waldron, J. Frederic Dewhurst
  - Item 12: Productivity Measurement, Publication (Box 66, Folder 20)
  - Item 13: Productivity and Employment, Publication (Box 66, Folder 20)
    Author: Stephen Raushenbush
- Box: 66, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 66, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Indexes of Output per Man-Hour for the Private Economy, 1966; Publication (Box 66, Folder 21)
  - Item 2: Indexes of Output per Man-Hour for Selected Industries, Publication (Box 66, Folder 21)
  - Item 3: Review of Productivity, Wages, and Prices, 1969; Publication (Box 66, Folder 21)
    Notes: May 1, 1969
  - Item 4: Raising Productivity, 1959; Publication (Box 66, Folder 21)
  - Item 5: The Productivity of Rural Workers on Industrial Jobs, 1964; Publication (Box 66, Folder 21)
    Author: Robert W. Lewis
  - Item 6: Solving Problems of Productivity in a Free Society, 1962; Publication (Box 66, Folder 21)
- Box: 66, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 66, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Productivity in the United Arab Republic, 1961; Publication (Box 66, Folder 22)
    Author: Mohamed I. Dessouki
    Notes: December 4, 1961
  - Item 2: Employment and Productivity Growth in New Zealand Manufacturing Industries, Publication (Box 66, Folder 22)
    Author: C.A. Blyth, P. Hamer
- Box: 66, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 66, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: A Performance Analysis System, Publication (Box 66, Folder 23)
    Author: William A. Gill
  - Item 2: The Measuring of Work in the Office, Publication (Box 66, Folder 23)
  - Item 3: A Performance Analysis System, 1953; Publication (Box 66, Folder 23)
- Box: 66, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 66, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Productivity of Labor in Agricultural Production, Publication (Box 66, Folder 24)
    Author: Folke Dovring
  - Item 2: Gains in Productivity of Farm Labor, 1950; Publication (Box 66, Folder 24)
    Author: Reuben W. Hecht, Glen T. Barton
  - Item 3: Agriculture, Publication (Box 66, Folder 24)
- Box: 66, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 66, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: The Productivity of Agricultural Labor in the Export Crops of Guatemala, Publication (Box 66, Folder 25)
    Author: Lester Schmid
- Box: 66, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 66, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Indexes of Output per Man-Hour, 1964; Publication (Box 66, Folder 26)
- Box: 66, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 66, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Case Study Data on Productivity and Factory Performance, 1953; Publication (Box 66, Folder 27)
    Notes: October 1953